<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dev.log</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on dev.log</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dealing With procrastination #2 - Pomodoro</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2017-07-10-dealing-with-procrastination-pomodoro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2017-07-10-dealing-with-procrastination-pomodoro/</guid>
      <description>Work for 25 minutes, rest 5.
 The Pomodoro Technique is a time management method developed by Francesco Cirillo in the late 1980s. The technique uses a timer to break down work into intervals, traditionally 25 minutes in length, separated by short breaks. These intervals are named pomodoros, the plural in English of the Italian word pomodoro (tomato), after the tomato-shaped kitchen timer that Cirillo used as a university student.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms day 1 - Hanoi towers</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2017-07-09-hanoi-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2017-07-09-hanoi-tower/</guid>
      <description>To undetstand recursion, You must first undestand recursion
 The Tower of Hanoi (also called the Tower of Brahma or Lucas&amp;rsquo; Tower[1] and sometimes pluralized) is a mathematical game or puzzle. It consists of three rods and a number of disks of different sizes, which can slide onto any rod.
The puzzle starts with the disks in a neat stack in ascending order of size on one rod, the smallest at the top, thus making a conical shape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with procrastination #1 - daily TODO</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2017-07-05-dealing-with-procrastination-daily-todo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2017-07-05-dealing-with-procrastination-daily-todo/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR write a list of tasks to complete for the next day.
 Procrastination (from latin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;procrastinare&amp;rdquo;, that translates in to : the prefix pro-, &amp;lsquo;forward&amp;rsquo;, and suffix -crastinus, &amp;lsquo;till next day&amp;rsquo; from cras, &amp;lsquo;tomorrow&amp;rsquo; ) is the avoidance of doing a task that needs to be accomplished.Sometimes, procrastination takes place until the &amp;ldquo;last minute&amp;rdquo; before a deadline. Procrastination can take hold on any aspect of life—putting off cleaning the stove, repairing a leaky roof, seeing a doctor or dentist, submitting a job report or academic assignment or broaching a stressful issue with a partner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pg_repack - full vacuum without table lock </title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2017-07-05-pg_repack-full-vacuum-without-locking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2017-07-05-pg_repack-full-vacuum-without-locking/</guid>
      <description>In PostgreSQL, an UPDATE or DELETE of a row does not immediately remove the old version of the row. If you have application that does this massive batch UPDATEs or DELETEs your database can grow in size pretty quickly.
At [ISE][ise] we develop plant performance monitoring application which collects hundreds (somtimes &amp;gt; 1000) of data counters ever minute. This &amp;ldquo;minute-by-minute&amp;rdquo; data is later compressed into hourly slots. This process involves massive DELETE operations every hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://example.org/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Father, husband, dog owner, software engineer (my wife would argue about the order).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>